{"data":[{"question":"Why does everybody like Mrs Rose?  \" Because she always good _________ after-dinner jokes.\"","a":"says","b":"speaks","c":"to tell","d":"tells","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Tell (plural tells): A reflexive, often habitual behavior, esp. one occurring in a context that often features attempts at deception by persons under psychological stress (e.g., a poker game or police interrogation), that reveals (gives away) information that the person exhibiting the behavior is attempting to withhold","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"While in his college days he used to _________ long hair.","a":"have","b":"wear","c":"reserve","d":"grow","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: if something used to happen, it happened regularly or all the time in the past, but does not happen now\n- Wear:  to have your hair or beard in a particular style or shape","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you see her? \" She _________ her hair in curls.\"","a":"have","b":"wear","c":"set","d":"reserve","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Set: to arrange someone's hair while it is wet so that it has a particular style when it dries","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"These two girls are very popular in town. \" Every boy here wants ___ \"","a":"to date them","b":"a date with them","c":"dating","d":"and dates them","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A date with somebody: an occasion when you go out with someone that you like in a romantic way \n- Want sth\/to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You seem to have a lot of money with you. \" Yes, the store ___\"","a":"cashed a check at me","b":"cashed a check to me","c":"cashed me a check","d":"cashed to me a check","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Cash sbd sth \n- Cash a cheque\/postal order\/draft etc: to exchange a cheque etc for the amount of money it is worth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The professor ___ us we could leave.","a":"said","b":"asked","c":"told","d":"spoke","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Speak: to talk to someone about something. \n- Tell: if someone tells you something, they communicate information, a story, their feelings etc. to you. \n- Say: to express an idea, feeling, thought etc using words- Sbd ask someone to do sth\/for sth \n- Ask somebody to do something\/for something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How did you get that green album? \" It was ___ from my father.\"","a":"gift for me","b":"gift to me","c":"a gift to me","d":"a gift for me","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use \"a\" before a noun that be used for first time \n- A gift to sbd","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The university owed ___ for the construction of the laboratory.","a":"to the builders thirty million dollars","b":"thirty million dollars on the builders","c":"for the builders thirty million dollars","d":"the builders thirty million dollar","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Owe somebody money\/","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you do ? \" I mailed ___.\"","a":"at him the letter","b":"the letter on him","c":"the letter to him","d":"the letter at him","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Mail something to somebody","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Yesterday was my birthday. \"My mother ___\"","a":"made a cake to me","b":"made a cake me","c":"made for me a cake","d":"made me a cake","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Make somebody something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}